Thorton Hall 912, 1600 Holloway Ave, San Francisco, CA 94132 1 (415) 767-8984

m.cadier.kim@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

I build machine vision software for medical applications and backends for image storage. I also do research in combinatorial optimization, matroid theory and submodular functions, and I like to think about combinatorially inspired algorithms. I am also interested in transfer learning and convolutional neural networks for training on medical data.

WORK HISTORY

Machine Vision Engineer

San Francisco, CA

UCSF Proctor Foundation May, 2015 - present

Funded by a grand, I investigated and developed a pipeline and machine learning algorithms to classify images of eyelids. I worked with the PI to define the direction of the project and was the principal developer of the grading application.

Lecturer in Mathematics

San Francisco State University

San Francisco, CA

September, 2014 - December, 2015

I was the principal instructor for several sections of college algebra and precalculus. I helped develop and administer a large online calculus course for 200+ students.

Data Scientist San Mateo, CA Argyle Data June, 2014 - February, 2015

I prototyped statistical machine learning algorithms for time series analysis and fraud

detection in network data as well as implemented production versions in Java.

Languages/ Tools English French (Fluent) Java Python Matlab Julia C++

working with: AWS OpenCV Scikit-learn

Papers

A Characterization of Generalized Permutohedra for the Classical Reflection

Groups, 2015, (thesis)

Discriminating Eyelids with Trachomatous Inflammation - Follicular, with Dr.

Travis Porco and Dr. Kazunori Okada, 2015, (in progress)

EDUCATION

SFSU: MA, Mathematics, 2015

SFSU: BA, Philosophy, Mathematics, Computer Science, 2012

University of Paris 1 Pantheon la Sorbonne: Visiting Student , Philosophy,

Logic, Mathematics, 2009-2011